Guide to the Douglass Cecil North Papers, 1942-2012 and undated RL.00955
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1953-2012 and undated; 6
  - Writings by Others, 1965-2001 and undated; 5
    - Wilson, Robert. Reputation in Games and Markets, 1985 (Box 87)
    - Winston, Gordon. Productivity-reducing Effects of Supply Side Policies: Subsidizing Decreased Utilization, 1989 (Box 87)
    - Wold, Herman. Theoretical Empiricism: A General Rationale for Scientific Model-Building, 1985 (Box 87)
    - Wold, Herman. Systems Analysis by Partial Least Squares, 1983 (Box 87)
    - Wyman, Katrina Miriam. Sinking States., Approx. 2010 (Box 91)
    - Yan, Ji. Minimum Cigarette Purchase Age, Maternal Smoking and Infant Health., 2009 (Box 91)
    - Zajac, Edward E. Telecommunications: An Example of Policy Gone Awry? undated (Box 88)
    - Zarnowitz, Victor. Recent Work on Business Cycles in Historical Perspective: Review of Theories and Evidence, 1984 (Box 88)
    - Zevin, Robert B. The Use of a 'Long Run' Learning Function: With Application to a Massachusetts Cotton Textile Form, 1823-1860, 1968 (Box 88)
    - Zumbansen, Peer and Calliess, Gralf-Peter. Law, Economics and Evolutionary Theory: Introduction., 2009 (Box 91)
    - Zupan, Mark A. The Last-Period Problem in Politics: Do Congressional Representatives not Subject to a Reelection Constraint Alter Their Voting Behavior? 1988 (Box 88)